troybilt.com 2004-07-18

# Troy-Bilt Tillers, Chipper Shredder Vacuums, Snow Blowers, Mowers

|   
|  | 

**Troy-Bilt Commercial Privacy Notice**  
Effective April 1, 2001

**Our Commitment To Privacy  
**Your privacy is important to us. To better protect your privacy we provide this notice explaining our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used. 

**The Information We Collect  
**This notice applies to all information collected or submitted on the MTD Products Inc Website. On some pages, you can order products, make requests, register to receive mailings about new products or upcoming events or enter contests. The types of personal information voluntarily submitted and collected at these page are:

• Name  
• Address  
• Email address  
• Phone number  
• Credit/Debit Card Information  
• Serial and model numbers  
• Product Registration  
• Survey Information (This may include age, household description, lawn care/outdoor power product ownership/purchase information) 

If you opt not to provide us with personally identifiable information no material consequence will result, although you may be unable to participate in certain promotions, order product or receive product information offered through our Website. On some pages, you can submit information about other people. For example, if you order a gift online and want it sent directly to the recipient, you will need to submit the recipient's address. In this circumstance, the types of personal information collected are:

• Name  
• Address /Phone Number 

**Cookies  
**In order to offer and provide customer service, we may use cookies to record session information, such as items added to shopping carts, and to aid in ordering product. For example, we may use cookies to help remind us who you are and to deliver content and services based on your account information. Cookies are simply pieces of information that are sent to your browser from a Web server and stored on your computer's hard drive. The use of cookies is relatively standard and you will likely find them used on most other major Websites. Most browsers are initially set up to accept cookies. If you prefer, you can reset your browser either to notify you when you receive a cookie, or to refuse to accept cookies. 

**The Way We Use Information  
**You can register with our Website if you would like to receive updates on our new products and services or upcoming events. If you no longer wish to receive such mailings, please contact us at [service@mtdproducts.com](mailto:service@mtdproducts.com) and provide us with your exact name and e-mail and postal addresses. We use non-identifying information, such as your domain name, and aggregate information on what pages consumers access or visit to better design our Website, to help identify customer services issues and internally for marketing purposes.

 **Our Commitment To Data Security  
**Unfortunately, no data transmission over the Internet can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. Accordingly, despite our efforts to protect your personal information, we cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit to us, or to or from our online products or services. You transmit all such information at your own risk. However, once we receive your transmission, we make our best effort to ensure its security on our systems. 

We have put in place appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to protect against the loss, misuse or alteration of information under our control. 

**Our Commitment To Children's Privacy  
**Protecting the privacy of the very young is especially important. For that reason, we never collect or maintain information at our Website from those we actually know are under 13, and no part of our Website is structured to attract anyone under 13. If a child has provided us with personally identifiable information, a parent/guardian may follow the procedures below to access a child's information and to request the information be deleted from our records. We will make reasonable efforts to delete the child's information from our databases. 

**How You Can Correct Your Information  
**You can access all your personally identifiable information that we collect online and maintain and correct or delete it by contacting us in writing at the address below. We use this procedure to better safeguard your information. Our system does not accept corrections by e-mail. 

To protect your privacy and security, we also take reasonable steps to verify your identity before granting access or making corrections. 

**How To Contact Us  
**Should you have other questions or concerns about this privacy statement, please send us an email at [iparts@mtdproducts.com](mailto:iparts@mtdproducts.com) or write us at:

Webmaster  
MTD Products Inc  
P. O. Box 368022  
Cleveland, OH 44136-9722  
(330) 225-2600
